studentloanhero.com 2015-12-23

# Student Loan Hero - Privacy Policy | Refinance and Consolidate Your Student Loans | Student Loan Hero

### STUDENT LOAN HERO, INC. PRIVACY POLICY

Thanks for using http://studentloanhero.com (the “Site”). At Student Loan Hero, Inc. (“SLH”), we are committed to protecting your privacy. We have created this privacy policy to make sure you know what information we collect and how we use it. By using the Site, you expressly consent to the collection, storage, disclosure and use of your information as we have outlined in this Privacy Policy and you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we make any changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email. We also encourage you to check back, from to time, and review this Privacy Policy so that you always will know what personally identifiable information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the Site will be subject to the then current Privacy Policy.

### But first, a note about your use of the Site:

At the time you register for a SLH account, you will choose and provide us with an email address, password, social security number date of birth, bank account login credentials and Federal PIN. In addition, with your permission we will upload your student loan information to our Site in order to provide recommendations on how you should pay back your student loans. When you login and use the Site and give us permission to access your student loan data, your information and activities will be visible to us, but to no other person.

### What information do we collect?

##### Information provided by you:

You may provide us with certain personally identifiable information when you:

  * register for a SLH account;
  * login and actually use the Site;
  * request customer support or send us any other communication;
  * sign up for newsletters, email alerts, and special offers;
  * respond to surveys;
  * give us permission and the information necessary to upload your student loan information;
  * register for an advanced profile which will include your personal income, employment status, household size, college enrollment status and other demographic data.

Such information may include your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, student loan balances and terms, account numbers, lenders, social security number, and Federal PIN. You may also provide us with information about other people, such as their email addresses, if you email a product to a friend or refer a friend to the Site or our promotions.

### Information collected by Cookies:

SLH uses cookies on the Site to improve the quality of our site and services to you. A cookie is a small text file on your computer which a website sends to your computer to allow the website to store information which uniquely identifies our users. SLH’s cookies do not collect or store personally identifiable information. Rather, the cookie stores a token which uniquely identifies a particular user at a particular time. That token is then linked to the user information in our secured databases. You can always delete the cookies and reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to display a message when a cookie is being sent. If you reset your browser, some of the Site features and functionality may not be available to you and you may not be able to take advantage of all the features on the Site.

We may work with other companies who place cookies or web beacons on our website. These companies help operate our websites and provide you with additional products and services. They are subject to confidentiality agreements with SLH and other legal restrictions. SLH does not permit any of these companies to collect personal information using cookies or web beacons on our websites. Certain functionalities related to the provision of additional products and services require marketers to share website usage information about visitors to the Site, who have received a targeted promotional campaign, with a reputable third-party advertising company for the purpose of targeting future campaigns and upgrading visitor information used in reporting statistics. To this end, SLH’s third-party advertising company makes a note of some of the pages you visit on the Site through the use of pixel tags.

### Information collected by Web Beacons and Log Files:

SLH collects certain non-personally identifiable information through the use of web beacons and log files. Such information may include your IP address, browser type, site usage, and whether you opened emails you received from us.

### How do we secure your information?

When you place orders or access your account information, we use commercially reasonable and generally-accepted technological safeguards to secure any information we collect about you. You will be automatically logged out of your SLH account after fifteen minutes of non-activity. The secure server software (SSL) we use encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. In addition, your SLH account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. You should always take steps to protect the confidentiality of the password you select. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

##### We use the following specific measures to protect your SLH account and data we store about you:

  * 256-bit encryption issued by Comodo SSL;
  * 2048-bit next generation SSL certificates as recommended by the National Institute of Standards and Technology;
  * All access to SLH servers is secured and restricted from access by any external sources;
  * Recurring scans provided by McAfee Secure to detect and correct any security vulnerabilities.

We operate internationally and many of our computer systems are currently based in the United States. As a result, your personal data will be processed by us in the United States where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create a user account with us, you agree to this Privacy Policy and you consent to the transfer of all information you provide to us in the United States.

You may also choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our website.

We work very hard to protect your privacy, but we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee complete security.  
How do we use your information?

We use the personally identifiable information you provide to:

  * provide the features and functionality of the Site;
  * send you information about our products and services;
  * for our internal business purposes, such as data analysis, audits and so forth;
  * help us create content and show advertisements that are most relevant to you; and
  * send you information about third party products and services

We use your email address to communicate with you about your account and to send you certain notification emails. We may use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send marketing messages and notifications from time-to-time whether or not you created an account with us.

You may unsubscribe by visiting your profile page.

We use non-personally identifiable information to monitor the use and performance of the Site so that we can learn more about how people use the Site which helps us improve our products and services and significantly enhance your experience on our website.

Generally, SLH does not share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies without your consent except that:

SLH provides information to its agents and trusted service providers and contractors for limited purposes, such as providing customer service; managing information on our behalf; and enhancing the Site’s features and functionality. In such cases, we require that these parties agree to use the information solely for the purpose for which we provided it to them and in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

If you sign up for a promotion or enroll in a service we offer in partnership with a third party, we may provide information (such as your name, email address, and account activity) to such third parties.

SLH may also release information (including your name, addresses, telephone number, and account activity) when we, in our sole discretion believe that such release is necessary or appropriate to:

  * comply with law;
  * comply with subpoenas, warrants, court orders, government investigations, or other legal process;
  * enforce or apply the terms of any of our user or license agreements;
  * investigate or respond to allegations of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other unlawful activity
  * investigate fraud or similar claims;
  * protect the rights, property or safety of SLH, our users, or others.
  * to protect our operations; or
  * to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

SLH may disclose non-personally-identifiable information to third parties in aggregate form to potential business partners and investors.

### Advertising

SLH may use third party service providers to place ads on our behalf across the internet and sometimes on the Site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Site, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a web beacon, which is industry standard technology used by most major sites. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service providers, please contact us at info@studentloanhero.com.

In addition, we will offer our users the opportunity to opt-in to receive emails, notifications of promotions and the like offered by our partners from such partners. You have the right to decline to opt-in to take advantage of this service.

### Does this Privacy Policy apply when I access third party websites?

You may be able to access third party websites directly from the Site. However, this Privacy Policy does not apply when you access third party websites. We cannot control how third parties may use personal information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third party website you visit before using it or disclosing your personal information to its provider.

### How can I change, delete, or update my information?

Your private account information can be changed in the Profile section of the Site. If you have any questions about what information is stored or would like to modify or obtain a copy of such information, please contact us at

info@studentloanhero.com or

Student Loan Hero, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
330 A Street  
Suite 135  
San Diego, CA 92101

After receiving proof of your identity, we will provide the information to you, and you may request that we delete or change any or all of the information.

Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

The current version of the SLH Privacy Policy was adopted effective as of September 3, 2012.
